[
    {
      "question": " Which of the following is the correct identifier ?",
  
      "option1": " $var_name",
  
      "option2": " VAR_123",
  
      "option3": " varname@",
  
      "option4": " None of the above",
  
      "answer": " VAR_123"
},
    {
        "question": " Which of the following is the address operator ?",
    
        "option1": " @",
    
        "option2": " #",
    
        "option3": " &",
    
        "option4": " %",
    
        "answer": " &"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the following features must be supported by any programming language to become a pure object-oriented programming language ?",
    
        "option1": " Encapsulation",
    
        "option2": " Inheritance",
    
        "option3": " Polymorphism",
    
        "option4": " All of the above",
    
        "answer": " All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": " The programming language that has the ability to create new data types is called___.",
    
        "option1": " Overloaded",
    
        "option2": " Encapsulated",
    
        "option3": " Reprehensible",
    
        "option4": " Extensible",
    
        "answer": " Extensible"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the following is the correct syntax to read the single character to console in the C++ language ?",
    
        "option1": " Read ch()",
    
        "option2": " Getline vh()",
    
        "option3": " get(ch)",
    
        "option4": " Scanf(ch)",
    
        "answer": " get(ch)"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the following statements is correct about the formal parameters in C++ ?",
    
        "option1": " Parameters with which functions are called",
    
        "option2": "  Parameters which are used in the definition of the function",
    
        "option3": "  Variables other than passed parameters in a function",
    
        "option4": "  Variables that are never used in the function",
    
        "answer": "  Parameters with which functions are called"
      },
      {
        "question": "The C++ language is ______ object-oriented language.",
    
        "option1": " Pure Object oriented",
    
        "option2": " Not Object oriented",
    
        "option3": " Semi Object-oriented or Partial Object-oriented",
    
        "option4": " None of the above",
    
        "answer": " Semi Object-oriented or Partial Object-oriented"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the following comment syntax is correct to create a single-line comment in the C++ program ?",
    
        "option1": " //Comment",
    
        "option2": " /Comment/",
    
        "option3": " Comment//",
    
        "option4": " None of the above",
    
        "answer": " //Comment"
      },
      {
        "question": " C++ is a ___ type of language.",
    
        "option1": " High-level Language",
    
        "option2": " Low-level language",
    
        "option3": " Middle-level language",
    
        "option4": " None of the above",
    
        "answer": " Middle-level language"
      },
      {
        "question": " Which of the following refers to characteristics of an array ?",
    
        "option1": " An array is a set of similar data items",
    
        "option2": " An array is a set of distinct data items",
    
        "option3": " An array can hold different types of datatypes",
    
        "option4": " None of the above",
    
        "answer": " An array is a set of similar data items"
      }
    
    
    
]